

# Zorica Vrchkovska

Adress: Skoevska 112 7000 Bitola

phone: +38978293951

email:vrckovskazo@gmail.com

Highly motivated and persuasive person with professional skills, deep sense of responsibility and experience and wide range of extra curriculum trainings, especially in management and business. Experienced in working with M. Office. Analytic, responsible and proficient in English language. Freelancer/Online Tutor for English language. Ready for new challenges, good team player and flexible personality.

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

Freelancer - writer and manager of fb page for translation English to Macedonian and writing texts in both languages

Sep.2008-ongoing

Management and advertisement: payed Facebook adds, Updating content, writing a blog Follow up of inquiries Dealing with multiple projects

Call - center operator (home based)
IFF International Palermo Italy

Aug.2020 - Sept.2020

Administrative work: managing email, briefing Working on different project – making surveys (B2B, B2C) Other tasks

Administrative assistant – office manager/ Technologist – engineer Kobil Bitola

Dec.2018 - Sept. 2019

Administrative work: managing email, writing proposals
Development in technologies in producing decorative panels
Supervising decorative panels production department
Marketing and developing relations with companies from abroad
Other tasks

### Technologist Hemipak - Bitola

Mar. 2018 - Dec. 2018

Probes for development of new products in hygiene Work with carton semi products Administrative work Other tasks

# Administrative assistant in governmental and public tenders CENTER FOR PUBLIC HEALTH BITOLA

Dec.2015 - Nov. 2017

Tender documentation for governmental and public tenders, e-tenders, collaboration with other departments regarding tenders

Telephone alerting for the debt to the companies (especially debt for 2013 and 2014)

Work on program for storage evidention

Collaboration with Department for social medicine – in making texts

Other administrative work

# Operator in Cutting Kromberg&Subert

June 2015-Nov. 2015 Bitola, R.Macedonia

Working on a machine with highly specific software in 3 shifts Making a half – made products for the factory departments Checking of the product for any irregularity

#### **Volunteering – SZIP OPERATOR**

Jan. 2013 – July 2013

### Ministry for agriculture, Bitola

Drawing of agriculture parcels on computer program Work with clients

Other administrative work

Bitola, Macedonia

#### **EDUCATION**

### Dipl. Biotechnologist

2004 - 2008

University St. Kliment Ohridski Bitola

Bitola, Macedonia

#### SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

Motive and result orientation Maximum quality for services to clients Excellent communication skills

Zorica Vrchkovska

## Ability for independent work Excellent computer skills (Excel, Word, Outlook, P.Point)

#### CERTIFICATES

- Certificate for Computing Government of R.Macedonia, 2008
- Certificate for Computing Government of R.Macedonia, 2008
- Certificate for English language (B2 level) Logos Oxford, 2010
- Certificate for Internet tools and applications American corner Bitola, 2011
- Certificate for governmental and public tenders Biro for governmental and public tenders, Ministry of finance, 2016
- Certificate for e-system for governmental and public tenders TD Consulting Skopje, 2017
- Certificate for management skills Motiva Skopje, 2017
- International Certificate for HACCP implementation COP Bitola, 2017
- International Certificate for quality of food and Nutrition COP Bitola, 2017
- Junior PHP/MySQL/Data developer Javen Advertajzing Bitola, 2019